# **Huynh Minh Tien**

## **Summary**

I have been studying the Business Administration major at FPT University, which brought me advanced skills in the economic field. I highly would like to experience and work for a company with a professional and cordial environment. Besides, I have a hard-working attitude, a willingness to learn new things and want to challenge myself. So, I believe I have enough quality to apply for our company as a long-term employee.



### Education -

**FPT UNIVERSITY SEP 2020 - NOW** 

Major: Business Administration

#### BINH LONG SPECIALIZED AND GIFTED HIGH SCHOOL

SEP 2017 - AUG 2020

Specialized Math, average score 9.3



# **Work Experience -**

**FPT UNIVERSITY SEP 2020 - NOW** 

Advising education enrollment

My job was to called the client and proposed for them the new services. After 6 months working with FPT University I have great skill in:

- + Talking and understand what the client want.
- + Persuasive and patience.
- + Customer care
- + Solving problem.



### **FPT CHESS CLUB**

OCT 2020 - MAY 2021

Member of club in university

- Organize monthly chess-playing events, network members.
- Share communication skills, group activities skills.

### **PUBLIC PROJECT - TRÁI QUA-RANTINE**

SEP 2021 - NOV 2021

Member of builder group

- Mentioning events in the social distancing period, network members.
- Share homing skills, public connection skills.



Tran Thi Mai Phuong Manager of Admissions Department Email: Phuongttm13@fe.edu.vn

Mobile: 02873001866



- March 3,2002
- Male
- +84879716939
- minhtien3302@gmail.com
- National University B Dormitory, Dong Hoa, Di An, Binh Duong, Vietnam
- fb.com/minhtien.huynh.5682

### SKILLS

Communicate

Computer

Teamwork

Flexibility and Creativity